Miss Cangyue.
So much medicine.
Which one can knock out the tyrant?
Sleeping potion.
This is too straightforward.
Cangyue.
Why is he here?
He...
Could he have found out?
Since I came to this world,
he is the only one to approach me for no reason.
But I always feel he's not that simple.
What are you doing here?
Me?
The young prince felt the medicine was too bitter a few days ago.
I know a little about pharmacology
and should be able to help.
So I came to take a look.
Did you figure out a way?
Fang Hai.
Add white quartz together, and then
eat more candied fruit.
What Miss Cangyue said seems to make some sense.
However, eating too much candied fruit can easily cause cavities.
It may need further study.
Of course.
Good thing I got away with it.
I want to see how far you can go.
Hello, game player.
According to the current progress,
you need to complete
the task objectives of the Holy Maiden of the Moon Shadow Clan as soon as possible,
so that you can get an unexpected surprise.
NPC progress 1%.
Your Majesty, the wine you ordered is here.
Your Majesty,
the wine you ordered is here.
Come up.
Yes.
Does he have some special fetishes?
Hurry up.
Come closer to me.
Once he passes out, I'll stab him in the heart,
and my mission will be over.
Want a drink?
No.
I'll feed you.
Your Majesty, please don't.
That's five doses of sleeping drugs.
What if it takes effect?
Your Majesty, no.
[Coughs]
Why not?
Not here.
Then where do you want to be?
How about the Imperial Garden?
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, I am not feeling well today.
Experiencer's character goal 10% complete.
All women in the palace are mine.
Do you think I care about how you feel?
You're this drunk after just one cup.
How is His Majesty doing lately?
His Majesty has taken a fancy to a new maid lately.
He is enjoying himself immensely.
He won't even spare the Imperial Garden.
Hahaha.
It's even more absurd than we thought.
Go and add some fuel to the fire.
Being just a tyrant is not enough.
Promiscuous
and ruthless,
that is what the Emperor of Donglin should be like.
Yes, hahaha.
Your Majesty, what are you doing? Your Majesty!
How dare you drug me.
Then I'll turn you into a human swine for my amusement.
Thank goodness it was just a dream.
Your Majesty.
The sun must have risen from the west.
I've been by your side for so many years,
but I've never seen any girl who served you
survive on this dragon bed.
She didn't serve me.
What?
She is a lightweight.
One cup and she was out.
I haven't stooped so low
as to be worse than a beast.
That's true.
After all, it's fine wine offered as tribute from the Western Regions.
No one in this world can match Your Majesty's alcohol tolerance.
Isn't he capable of all evil?
How could it be?
Your Majesty.
The Grand Princess has recently taken a liking to another girl.
She says the palace cannot be without an Empress for a single day.
She looks like a beauty from the Western Regions.
Why not present her to you?
Ah, no, no.
Good thing Her Royal Highness lives outside the palace.
Otherwise, Your Majesty, you'd have to listen to her nagging every day.
The things my aunt wants to manage...
I can handle more than just this matter.
Zhou Jin.
Cen Zhoujinxuan.
Jin Cen Zhoujin.
Ning Feihai.
Liang Quan Huiyong.
Xu Li.
Ming.
Rongming.